{
  "men": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "When is Scott's Birthday?",
        "options": ["8/1", "8/2", "8/3", "8/4", "8/5"],
        "answer": "8/2"
      },
      {
        "question": "True or False:  Scott is older than Lisa.",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer": "False"
      },
      {
        "question": "True or False:  Scott and Lisa were born in the same hospital.",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "What color are Scott's eyes?",
        "options": ["Blue", "Brown", "Green", "Hazel", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "All of the above"
      },
      {
        "question": "Regardless of what Scott says, how tall is he actually?",
        "options": ["5'11\"", "6'0\"", "6'1\"", "6'2\"", "6'3\""],
        "answer": "6'2\""
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Scott’s favorite cocktail?",
        "options": ["Dark & Stormy", "Gin & Tonic", "Mojito", "Margarita", "Whisky Sour"],
        "answer": "Gin & Tonic"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many girls did Scott date before meeting Lisa?",
        "options": ["1-10", "11-20", "21-30", "31-40", "> 50 (what a slut)"],
        "answer": "11-20"
      },
      {
        "question": "What year did Scott and Lisa start dating?",
        "options": ["1991", "1992", "1993", "1994", "1995"],
        "answer": "1993"
      },
      {
        "question": "On which # date did Scott first have sex with Lisa?",
        "options": ["2", "4", "6", "8", "10"],
        "answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Scott’s favorite sex position?",
        "options": ["Doggy Style", "Girl on Top", "Missionary", "Reverse Cowgirl", "Sixty-Nine"],
        "answer": "Sixty-Nine"
      }
    ],
    "number": 69
  },
  "women": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "When is Lisa's Birthday?",
        "options": ["6/26", "6/27", "6/28", "6/29", "6/30"],
        "answer": "6/27"
      },
      {
        "question": "True or False:  Lisa is older than Scott.",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "True or False:  Lisa and Scott were born in the same hospital.",
        "options": ["True", "False"],
        "answer": "True"
      },
      {
        "question": "What color are Lisa's eyes?",
        "options": ["Blue", "Brown", "Green", "Hazel", "All of the above"],
        "answer": "Brown"
      },
      {
        "question": "Regardless of what Lisa says, how tall is she actually?",
        "options": ["4'11\"", "5'0\"", "5'1\"", "5'2\"", "5'3\""],
        "answer": "5'1\""
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Lisa’s favorite cocktail?",
        "options": ["Dark & Stormy", "Gin & Tonic", "Mojito", "Margarita", "Whisky Sour"],
        "answer": "Dark & Stormy"
      },
      {
        "question": "How many guys did Lisa date before meeting Scott?",
        "options": ["1-10", "11-20", "21-30", "31-40", "> 50 (what a slut)"],
        "answer": "11-20"
      },
      {
        "question": "What year did Lisa and Scott start dating?",
        "options": ["1991", "1992", "1993", "1994", "1995"],
        "answer": "1993"
      },
      {
        "question": "On which # date did Lisa first have sex with Lisa?",
        "options": ["2", "4", "6", "8", "10"],
        "answer": "2"
      },
      {
        "question": "What is Lisa’s favorite sex position?",
        "options": ["Doggy Style", "Girl on Top", "Missionary", "Reverse Cowgirl", "Sixty-Nine"],
        "answer": "Girl on Top"
      }
    ],
    "number": 27
  },
  "whos-who": {
    "questions": [
      {
        "question": "Who is our youngest friend here?",
        "options": ["Adam the Adventurous", "Kelly the Kittenish", "Ryan the Relatable", "Sarah the Swollen", "Teddy the Thrilling"],
        "answer": "Kelly the Kittenish"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who is our oldest friend here?",
        "options": ["Christian the Cuddly", "Frank the Friendly", "John the Jovial", "Holly the Heavenly", "Tara the Terrific"],
        "answer": "Frank the Friendly"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who here has known Lisa longest?",
        "options": ["Lee the Lively", "Lisa the Lavish", "Lisa the Luscious", "Liz the Luminous", "Liza the Lovely"],
        "answer": "Lisa the Lavish"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who here has known Scott longest?",
        "options": ["Betsy the Benevolent", "Brian the Bohemian", "Jon the Jubilant", "Ryan the Relatable", "Won the Wondrous"],
        "answer": "Betsy the Benevolent"
      },
      {
        "question": "Who traveled the farthest for the celebration?",
        "options": ["Jason the Jovial", "Jim the Jolly", "Joey the Just", "Melissa the Masterful", "Scott the Scintillating"],
        "answer": "Jason the Jovial"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which bridesmaid was born in the contiguous United States?",
        "options": ["Annie the Auspicious", "Antje the Angelic", "Liz the Luminous", "Liza the Lovely", "Marines the Magnanimous"],
        "answer": "Liza the Lovely"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which groomsman was born in the contiguous United States?",
        "options": ["Alex the Affable", "Christian the Cuddly", "Evelio the Effervescent", "Brian the Bodacious", "Mitch the Merry", "Orr the Original"],
        "answer": "Brian the Bodacious"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which couple did not walk to the celebration?",
        "options": ["Donn the Dynamic & Holly the Heavenly", "Lee the Lively & Annie the Auspicious", "Michael the Mercurial & Susan the Suggestive", "Jon the Jovial & Liz the Luminous", "Tom the Talented & Jess the Joyous"],
        "answer": "Michael the Mercurial & Susan the Suggestive"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these couples are married?",
        "options": ["Andy the Amusing & Michelle the Mighty", "Jim the Joyful & Jeanne the Joyful", "Joey the Just and Kristina the Kind", "Scott the Scintillating & Porter the Passionate", "MaryPat the Mysterious and Cindy the Celestial"],
        "answer": "Andy the Amusing & Michelle the Mighty"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of these couples have fewer than 3 children?",
        "options": ["Bernie the Boisterous & Liza the Lovely", "Betsy the Benevolent & Anthony the Amusing", "Christian the Cuddly & Tina the Titillated", "Mitch the Merry & Tara the Terrific", "Orr the Original & Betsy the Bewitching"],
        "answer": "Orr the Original & Betsy the Bewitching"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which one of these friends has not been to a Phish show?",
        "options": ["Brian the Bohemian", "Carol the Colorful", "Jason the Jazzy", "Jason the Jovial", "Joey the Just", "Jon the Jubilant", "Jimmy the Jaunty", "Josh the Genuine", "Kristina the Kind", "Missy the Mindful", "Rob the Recalcitrant", "Ryan the Relatable"],
        "answer": "Josh the Genuine"
      },
      {
        "question": "Which of the following is not a Phish song? (Feel free to ask for help from a Phriend.)",
        "options": ["Glide", "Grind", "Stash", "Twist", "Turn"],
        "answer": "Turn"
      }
    ]
  }
}